The stipulation at the top of the contract
la estipulación de cima del contrato
established the non-appearance of the
establecía la incomparecencia del
program, that is, not going to the program, whatever
programa que no va al programa lo que
the refusal to follow the
sea la negativa a seguir las
instructions and directives of the
indicaciones y directrices de la
management, whoever has this in the
dirección quien tenga esto en el
contract, each worker will have their
contrato cada trabajador tendrá sus
conditions, obviously clear,
condiciones evidentemente claro todo el
not everyone will have it done, but whoever has
mundo no tendrá hecho pero quien tenga
this in the contract, from what I
esto en el contrato por lo que yo
understand, has to obey the
entiendo tienen que obedecer las
instructions and directives of the
indicaciones y las directrices de la
management, you are catching it if they do not listen
dirección lo estáis pillando si no hacen
to management and do not follow the
caso a la dirección y no siguen las
instructions and directives of the
indicaciones y las directrices de la
management, they are out on the street and on top of that,
dirección a la calle y encima indemnizan
they compensate the producer or whoever with
ellos a la productora oa quien sea con
12, there you have it,
12 ya está ahí lo tiene
there you have the opinions of more than one,
ahí tiene las opiniones de más de uno
but how the hell do you sign?
pero como firma